[{"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "130513pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "Now the interesting thing about him is at the moment, there's no DNA evidence linking him to any other crimes of this nature, not only in his own state, but also now nationally, is that right?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "Monster.", "docId": "130513pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "What is your brother to you now?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "What he did was monstrous but if we call him a monster, what we're doing is closing the book on understanding how this human being was able to create this prison in his own home and lock these three women up and the horrific acts and abuse that took place.", "docId": "130513pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "Is that what Ariel Castro is?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130513pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "Do you believe his brothers knew absolutely nothing?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "In that same note he also said, I was abused as a child by an uncle, and I want to give my money to my victims.", "docId": "130513pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "Could that be at the center of all the depravity that followed?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "What I read into that is this is somebody who may have very well have been abused.", "docId": "130513pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "What do you read into this?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "No --", "docId": "130513pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "He never sought it, though, did he?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "These three girls who -- young women and one of them a girl when she was kidnapped, have been through a horrific experience and they're all I'm sure suffering from trauma.", "docId": "130513pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "How you would think that may remedy itself?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "I think that it's likely that he offended somewhat and then it escalated.", "docId": "130513pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "And finally, is it likely, as seems to be the case at the moment, because of no DNA evidence to the contrary, that he didn't offend really until perhaps his 40s?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "Remember, 1989, he abused his wife.", "docId": "130513pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "What happened?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "It's possible.", "docId": "130513pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "Have they broken the law, the Justice Department, by doing this?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130513pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "I mean, that's all very well, but the reality is that here you have a real attack on the freedom of the press, don't you?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "Yes, it is very upsetting, but I think, Piers, that we're going to have to see what more there is to this story.", "docId": "130513pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "Let me ask you straight away, are you as appalled by this A.P. story as I am?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "No doubt about it.", "docId": "130513pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "But that again is an outrageous abuse of their position, isn't it?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "This is -- without a doubt, this has been a tough week.", "docId": "130513pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "Final question, briefly, if you don't mind, when you add the A.P. story, scandal, let's call it that -- the IRS scandal, the ongoing scandal of Benghazi, this has been the worst week the president's had, isn't it?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "It is, for the president.", "docId": "130513pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "This is a bad, bad week for Barack Obama, isn't it?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "I haven't heard from my former colleagues.", "docId": "130513pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "Have you had a good reaction?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "Well, I think so, because there are a number of people, both in the House and the Senate, that want to work together and get things done.", "docId": "130513pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "Do they want to hear this message?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "Well, he's certainly eligible for it.", "docId": "130513pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "Should he get the death penalty, do you think?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "Well, in this case, I initially thought that she had a great shot at getting life in prison.", "docId": "130513pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "What do you think will happen there?", "qSentId": 529}]